linoit.com 2009-06-20

# Privacy Policy - Infoteria Online Corporation

Infoteria Online Corporation’s policy regarding the protection of private information (Privacy Policy)

##  [Contents]

  * Purpose of this Privacy Policy 
  * Our policy regarding the protection of private information 
  * Information we collect 
  * How we use private user information 
  * Sharing of private user information 
  * Our policy regarding safe protection of data 
  * User selections available for receiving Email 
  * Information regarding cookies and browsers 
  * About the open forum 
  * Our policy regarding the protection of the private information of children 
  * Regarding links to other websites 
  * How to access, change, and update user information 
  * Contacting us 
  * Changes to this Privacy Policy 

## [Purpose of this Privacy Policy]

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to explain our policy regarding the handling of private information on the Infoteria Online Corporation (herein referred to as “Infoteria Online”) website and to provide information pertaining to the user choices regarding the handling of private information collected by Infoteria Online.  
Please be aware that services that Infoteria Online does not offer independently, such as websites with content offered in conjunction with a business partner, are handled under additional Privacy Policies and separate Privacy Policies.

## [Our policy regarding the protection of private information]

The protection of private user information is an important issue to Infoteria Online. In order to protect private user information, Infoteria Online has created a Privacy Policy explaining the common practices of Infoteria Online regarding private information and user choices regarding the methods of collecting, using, and disclosing private user information. In order to make this policy easy for users to find, it is accessible from the Infoteria Online website as well as in areas which require private information. 

## [Information we collect]

This Privacy Policy applies to all information collected by Infoteria Online including private information and all information provided to Infoteria Online. “Private Information” is information pertaining to living individuals, and refers to data which can identify a specific individual via a name, date of birth, and other statements included in such information (including data which can be easily compared to other information to identify a specific individual). Infoteria Online collects private information in the following instances. 

  * When a user account is created so that a user can become a member of the Infoteria Online website or other services that Infoteria Online offers 
  * When a user purchases Infoteria Online products and services online 
  * When a user conducts user registration 
  * When a user requests support for Infoteria Online products or services 
  * When a user requests information or resources from Infoteria Online (such as White Paper) 
  * When a user participates in Infoteria Online inspection and evaluation 
  * When a user participates in an Infoteria Online promotion contest or prize giveaway. 
  * When a user contacts or leaves a comment for Infoteria Online 
  * When a user seeks a job with Infoteria Online and replies to Infoteria Online recruiting 

Infoteria Online also collects private information with individual consent at meetings, trade shows, and expositions.  
Collected private information includes the following data (however, it is not limited to such). 

  * The user’s full name 
  * The user’s title and the name of the organization to which the user belongs 
  * Actual addresses such as the home address and the billing address of the user (prefecture and city name, etc.) 
  * The user’s Email address 
  * The user’s telephone number 
  * Any other information specified by the user for use when Infoteria Online contacts the user online or offline 
  * Information collected online and stored by Infoteria Online related to the user’s account, including the following information 
  * The user’s name for Infoteria Online services 
  * The user’s password for Infoteria Online services 
  * Information regarding the user’s credit card 

## [How we use private user information]

There is a case wherein Infoteria Online uses the private information collected from users for the following purposes.

  * Creating and maintaining user accounts 
  * Management and confirmation complying with user instruction 
  * Infoteria Online product registration for users 
  * Answering questions from users 
  * Registering users for programs (based on user request) 
  * Sending information to users 
  * Sending dossiers to users 
  * When considering applicants for employment 

Infoteria Online also uses this private information in order to supply information related to user accounts and products and services purchased by the user from Infoteria Online to the user, to better understand user needs, to improve Infoteria Online products and services, and to label items to be delivered with the appropriate name and address. 

## [Sharing of private user information]

Infoteria Online shall not share or provide private information supplied by the user to Infoteria Online to any third parties without user consent except for in the following cases. Infoteria Online can disclose/provide private information from the user to a third party in the following cases. 

  * When it is necessary to execute purchase orders, to manage invoices and credit cards, to provide services, and for Email housing (as the results of usage previously explained within this Privacy Plan) 
  * When it is required by law (when responding to valid summons, warrant, tax audit, or administrational institution measures or when preventing illicit acts). 
  * For survey activity such as submission of statistical reports (the collected information is used to explain Infoteria Online services to present and future partners and other third parties, and not used to contact the subjects of the reports). 
  * For corporate transactions such as mergers, buyouts, integrations, division sell-offs, etc. (usage of this information is conditional on the pledge by the receiving party stating compliance with a confidentiality agreement to refrain from using the information for any purpose other than the corporate transaction) 
  * When approved by laws related to the protection of private information. 

##  [Our policy regarding safe protection of data]

In addition to conducting employee training regarding the Infoteria Online Privacy Policy, Infoteria Online discloses the Infoteria Online Privacy Policy to Infoteria Online business partners as well. Also, Infoteria Online’s website uses a technology called Secure Socket Layer (SSL) which encodes private information when it is transmitted to the Infoteria Online website. Furthermore, Infoteria Online and business partners of Infoteria Online enter into a confidentiality agreement requiring caution and preventative measures in order to prevent the loss, misuse, and disclosing of private user information. 

## [User selections available for receiving Email]

Infoteria Online endeavors to provide an environment where users can opt in or out of receiving Email from Infoteria Online and Infoteria Online’s partners.   
Infoteria Online shall send Email to users in the following cases 

  * In order to send notifications to a user regarding that’s user account 
  * In order to send notifications to a user regarding products purchased by that user 
  * In order to send notifications to a user regarding services purchased by that user 
  * In order to answer questions and comments from users 

Also, Infoteria Online shall send to users Email which includes information regarding products and services which match each user’s interests and special information except for in the case wherein a user has opted to not receive such Email. In addition, with user consent, Infoteria Online’s business partners will also send such information to users. A user can communicate whether or not that user wishes to receive promotional materials, information, or special information from Infoteria Online or a business partner when creating a user account in the Infoteria Online website, when registering for any service, when the providing private user information to Infoteria Online, and when Infoteria Online sends an Email to the user. Note that when a user opts not to receive advertisement Email, that user cannot receive special information which may benefit that user.

Infoteria Online continually provides chances for users to opt out of direct marketing communication. All advertisement Email sent from Infoteria Online contains information which allows the user to chose to refuse receiving such Email in the future. Users can send a correspondence to Infoteria Online via any of the following addresses requesting for the termination of Email transmission, and can request a termination of transmission via Email as well. 

  * Email: online@Infoteria.co.jp 
  * Standard postal address: 

C/O Private Information Manager  
Infoteria Online Corporation  
10th Floor, NT Building   
1-47-1 Oi, Shinagawa-ku, Tokyo, Japan 140-0014  
In order to protect users, Infoteria Online shall contact users in the case wherein an issue arises necessitating immediate caution regarding a problem pertaining to products or services purchased by the user. 

## [Information regarding cookies and browsers]

Infoteria Online’s website automatically takes control of the user’s IP address. Controlled IP addresses are used to solve problems related to Infoteria Online’s server, for website management, and for safety management when the user uses the Infoteria Online website. Also, they are also used to identify users and user shopping carts. 

Also, in order to provide services that correspond to individual user demand, Infoteria Online stores user information and uses tracking cookies. A cookie is light data sent from a website to the user’s browser to be saved in the hard drive of the user’s computer. In some cases it is necessary for cookies to be received in the user’s browser for websites where logging in is required or for the Infoteria Online website, which provides individual user services.

If a user does not desire for private information to be stored via cookies, that user may set the cookie option in the browser to off or set the browser to request authorization for cookies each time they are sent. However, in some cases providing certain products and services require the use of cookies. Please be aware that turning cookies off will result in a lowering of performance and functionality of this website. Detailed information regarding the method for setting cookie authorization can be found in the user’s browser manual. 

##  [About the open forum]

The open forum consists of user oriented chat rooms, a forum, message board, news groups, etc. Be aware that information disclosed via such an online service generally becomes public material. Be careful when disclosing your own private information in this environment. Infoteria Online values each user’s opinion and facilitates freedom of speech. However, in order to maintain the forum, Infoteria Online reserves the right to take necessary steps, such as eliminating statements which disturb the public order. 

## [Our policy regarding the protection of the private information of children]

Due to our special concern for the privacy of children, Infoteria Online does not accept private information online from children that Infoteria Online knows to be 12 years old or younger. Infoteria Online will not allow anyone that Infoteria Online knows to be 12 years old or younger to become a registered member of the Infoteria Online website, nor will Infoteria Online allow such an individual to purchase products or services via the Infoteria Online website. Infoteria Online will also not collect or ask for private information from any individual that Infoteria Online knows to be 12 years old or younger. 

## [Regarding links to other websites]

The Infoteria Online website includes links to other websites. However, Infoteria Online bears absolutely no liability for the information collection practices of websites which can be accessed via links from the Infoteria Online website. If a problem arises concerning the information collection practices of such a website, contact the webmaster of that site directly. 

##  [How to access, change, and update user information]

Users are able to request alterations and updating of their own private information at any time. When this is necessary, write the details to be changed and send a request for alteration to online@Infoteria.co.jp via Email. 

## [Contacting us]

If users have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or the use of private user information by Infoteria Online, they may contact Infoteria Online via Email (online@Infoteria.co.jp) or by the following postal mail address.

C/O Private Information Manager, Administrative Department  
Infoteria Online Corporation  
10th Floor, NT Building   
1-47-1 Oi, Shinagawa-ku, Tokyo, Japan 140-0014

## [Changes to this Privacy Policy]

Infoteria Online possesses the right to alter the Infoteria Online policy regarding privacy as needed. When such an alteration occurs, a notice of the alteration will be listed on this website for a period of 30 days starting from the day of the alteration.

This Privacy Policy was last updated on Oct 22, 2007.
